-All good?
-Checks are complete.
IMMIGRATION OFFICER (MINISTRY OF JUSTICE)
KEIICHIRO HAYAMI
CUSTOMS OFFICER (MINISTRY OF FINANCE)
ATSUSHI MATSUYAMA
Creatine, approved. Zinc, approved.
Melatonin, requires confirmation.
Glutamine, approved,
assuming it matches the label.
They're just regular supplements!
There's nothing suspicious here!
In Japan, these are
pharmaceutical products,
not general dietary supplements.
They require a prescription
or fall under strict quantity limits.
Any personal supply
exceeding a two-month limit must--
Just hurry it up already!
What is she doing?
It's the rules.
You have a lot of these pills as well.
There are barely any!
Foreign visitors in Japan have more
than doubled over the last ten years.
Over 40 million visited last year.
We are, however,
nearing our limit at the front lines.
The problem lies
with the airport's structure itself.
Immigration is handled
by the Ministry of Justice,
Customs by the Ministry of Finance,
Quarantine by the Ministry of Health,
and the airport police by the National
Police Agency. Furthermore,
there is the Ministry of Land,
the Ministry of Foreign Affairs,
the Ministry of Defense,
the Digital Agency…
Airports are often called
a melting pot of races,
but they are also a melting pot
of government offices.
MIDORI SUGIHARA
COUNSELOR OF BORDER CONTROL REFORM
Information is split vertically,
and the front lines
are always one step behind.
CHIKA KUMAGAWA - GROUND STAFF
-Yes, this way.
-Please, forward.
Hello!
Flight 2 has arrived.
Guiding 57 passengers now.
To break down these vertical walls,
a special unit led by me
that transcends the boundaries
between ministries and agencies
will begin operation.
That operation is…
Don't say it like it's an afterthought.
Mori? What are you doing?
Well, this part got dirty.
We have to take good care of our things.
-She touched it…
-What, is that bad?
We only handle them
during basic inspections.
If anything happens, it leads to trouble.
Did you do this?
No…
What are you going to do about it?
Um, no, it wasn't me, uh…
Oh, come on…
Excuse me, ma'am.
Did something happen to your luggage?
My suitcase has been crushed.
I'll take care of this.
Thank you.
-This way, please.
-Go ahead.
-I'll take a look at your passport.
-Of course.
IMMIGRATION PASSPORT READING SYSTEM
2026, MARCH 22 - QUESTIONED AT HONG KONG
NOT DENIED ENTRY
-What did you come to Japan for?
-Just sightseeing.
How long will you stay for?
About five days.
Could you look at his luggage?
This way.
Huh?
Please open that man's luggage.
Is something suspicious about him?
I can't share details.
It's Immigration Intelligence.
Just open it up.
That's all I need you to do.
No, Customs makes its own determinations.
What are you trying to check for?
Immigration exams people.
Customs exams items.
Let's keep to our own domains.
Give me a reason.
I can't open it otherwise.
I am a professional at reading people.
-Is that seriously your reason?
-Yes.
What is this?
Don't be so arrogant,
Mr. Immigration Agent.
I am Hayami.
Customs officers are so hard-headed.
My name's Matsuyama!
What's wrong?
Chief Officer…
Excuse me…
-May I inspect this luggage?
-Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Fine.
This suitcase is heavy.
-Heavy?
-Yes.
Especially near the bottom.
Enough to crush the bag
that was underneath it.
Is there something heavy inside?
-The scale is there.
-Most likely the wheels.
These wheels are strange.
The wheels on all the other suitcases
were warm from the outside temperature,
but these wheels are as cool
as the air-conditioned room.
Meaning?
The material of these wheels isn't rubber.
It's a heavy metal with high thermal
conductivity and high specific gravity.
In other words, it's basically--
Don't touch that!
Whoa, whoa, whoa…
Oh my…
BORDER CONTROL
This morning
at Kanto International Airport,
the Metropolitan Police Department
arrested
a foreign national on suspicion
of attempting to smuggle gold bullion…
Why are the police getting all the credit?
Gate 24 wasn't mentioned even once!
Counselor Sugihara.
Congratulations on the launch
of the new unit.
Airport Director Ikeura.
TAKAHIRO IKEURA
DIRECTOR OF KANTO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
Breaking down the walls
between ministries and agencies.
A truly admirable concept.
However, as someone responsible
for running the airport,
I have been hearing some concerns.
Concerns?
When there's a problem,
who makes the decision,
and who takes the blame?
You need to make that clear.
Those of us on the ground
can't operate on ideals alone, you know.
Good day.
It doesn't seem like
all the ministries and agencies
are being very cooperative.
Everyone cares more about
their own turf than the country.
And the location is practically
a deserted island too.
Yes.
For now, it's a six-month trial operation,
handling mostly temporary
and charter flights.
Basically, we're being treated
as benchwarmers.
Benchwarmers, huh?
I suppose I am
an old hearing officer
nearing retirement myself.
You're Chief Hearing Officer.
Having you on board, Fukasawa,
gives me so much reassurance.
I'm honored.
Besides,
I actually like this team.
I heard it was a motley crew thrown
together from various departments,
but they seem like
quite an interesting group.
The next flight will be
the last one handled by Gate 24 today.
Ah, I'm exhausted…
I've been moving since the morning.
My feet have hit their limit.
My bangs have hit their limit too.
Everyone, just one last push.
Matsuyama, are you listening?
Did you see this?
Only 500 views.
Gate 24… It isn't
being talked about at all.
Excuse me, customs officer, personal web
browsing during work hours isn't allowed…
Aren't you guys in Immigration
and Quarantine frustrated too?
After all the effort
to launch this new unit…
But isn't the general public
pretty uninterested in Immigration,
Customs, and Quarantine anyway?
I feel like people
don't even know the difference.
It is not something
we should concern ourselves with.
Let through those who should be
and stop those who should not be.
That is all we need to do.
Exactly!
That is the exact mission
entrusted to Gate 24.
As expected of the Ministry of Justice!
As expected of a career official!
Is that guy a career official?
They say he's a future candidate
for management,
but he volunteered because he wanted
to work on the front lines,
and he went through
proper training before coming here.
Why go out of his way to do that?
Because if you don't know the front lines,
you can't design system policies.
Wonderful!
Those words are practically
the constitution!
Still, it's a problem
to only focus on people.
Over here, we have to look at the goods.
Danger isn't necessarily limited
to people, after all.
By the way, what's she about?
Well, I don't really know either.
I usually hear about most things,
but regarding that girl,
I've got zero information.
She just keeps wiping things down.
Mori.
Machi Mori.
Yes?
Where was your previous
field assignment, Mori?
Field assignment…
This is my first time.
Announcement for passengers.
Southeast Asia Airlines Flight 226
from Ho Chi Minh City
will arrive at Gate 24.
We'll take our luggage. Please proceed.
There are two booths.
Please proceed in the line.
What does she mean this is her first time?
I doubt she's a complete rookie, though.
She's wiping things again…
Passports, please.
Please take your luggage over here.
-Is this all your luggage?
-Yes.
-Do you have anything to declare?
-No.
That's all right.
Are you traveling?
-It's our honeymoon. Honeymoon.
-Yes.
My wife comes to Japan a lot.
She loves it here, so…
I can see that.
How long do you plan to stay?
Two weeks.
Please step this way and use this booth.
Could I have a moment with both of you?
-Please take their luggage.
-Okay.
This way.
Please, have a seat.
Why… Why did you bring us here?
It's just a formal check.
Excuse me. What do I do with this luggage?
Keep it with the passengers.
Please wait here a moment.
Did something happen again?
Hayami!
-Seike, what about the inspections?
-I had Natori take over for me?
Um…
I saw you do this earlier.
What is that?
That's a hand signal
we've established in Immigration.
It's a signal for a suspicious person.
I see. A hand signal…
So those two really are suspicious, right?
-Just tell me already.
-I said, this is Immigration Intelligence.
Excuse me…
To break down these vertical walls,
-What are you doing?
-starting today, a special unit led by me
that transcends the boundaries
between ministries and agencies
will begin operation.
That is what she said.
So, in other words, at Gate 24,
we share information,
right?
That's…
Yes. I was so happy about the whole thing,
I rewatched it many times.
These are the words
of Counselor Midori Sugihara
from the Cabinet Secretariat
Border Control Reform Office.
Gate 24
is a brand new system, so…
Indeed… Hayami.
-We should work as a team and share--
-Provided that
nothing leaks to the outside.
Of course.
You too.
Yes. Information is shared.
Confidentiality is strict.
Regarding that couple,
the husband is Samir Sadikov.
The wife is Lylea Sadikova.
Both are from the Zafaria Federation.
Before coming to Japan,
they stopped in Vietnam,
but they were refused entry
during local inspections.
I see.
The Counselor is here right now as well.
Let's listen to this together.
Excuse me.
Did you run an inquiry on that couple?
Yes, however,
the current situation
in Zafaria is unstable,
so we cannot make inquiries
with their local authorities,
and we haven't been able
to verify their identities yet.
I see.
Until things are clear,
we should consider having them wait
without permitting entry.
-Yes, sir.
-Hayami.
I'll leave the questioning
of those two to you.
-Understood.
-This is perfect.
Why not have Customs lend a hand as well?
Counselor Sugihara…
Customs as well?
There are things that can be seen
through the goods, aren't there?
Shall we give it a try?
This might be
an excellent opportunity
to demonstrate the value of Gate 24.
I want Immigration and Customs
to work together to find the answer
as to whether those two
should be allowed entry or not.
Yes, leave it to us.
Apologies for keeping you waiting.
What's going on? Can we go?
To help with that,
please let us ask a few questions.
Before coming to Japan,
you two were refused entry in Vietnam.
We don't know.
You don't know?
Because they didn't tell us.
I see.
May we check the contents of this luggage?
Here? You go through luggage here?
Of course, it's voluntary,
but if you cooperate,
the check will be finished quickly.
Okay, okay. I open.
-Are you okay?
-Get the first aid kit.
It's okay. It's fine. It's okay.
Just, please, check.
Thank you.
To ensure there are no mix-ups
upon return,
we will record
the condition of the contents.
I'll do it.
Okay then.
-Please do so.
-Yes.
So the couple shares one piece of luggage…
May I ask?
You two are newlyweds,
but when and where did you meet?
It was about, uh,
about five years ago. Through a friend.
I'm asking Lylea.
Wait, hold on…
Ah, this, yes, this. This is ours.
I'll show…
This is Lylea's family.
Lylea's family.
-Show.
-Oh, yes, um…
This… This is my older brother,
my parents, and my little sister.
My older brother introduced us.
Thank you.
They look like a close-knit family.
That was from the party
we threw at our place.
Is it a pair of dolls?
Very cute.
Yes.
They were a wedding gift.
Could we please just get this over with?
We have a hotel reservation, so…
Then, continuing with the questions…
Hayami.
I'm Iuchi from the Metropolitan Police
Department's International Crime Division.
-Tamai.
-Hello.
-Someone's here.
-We were called here.
Likewise, I'm Nakatsuka.
Hello.
You came because of those two.
Do you know something?
I'll cut straight to the conclusion.
Let those two enter.
Why? Are those two--
We can't share details.
It's police intelligence.
Are you familiar
with the Immigration Control Act?
This decision is the duty of Immigration.
You can't suddenly ask us to grant entry
without a formal request.
Shut up. It's always
every little thing with you guys.
This matter involves
a criminal investigation.
End of story.
You guys just need
to open and close the doors.
Wait. What do you mean?
They were refused entry in Vietnam,
but the Japanese police
are telling us to let them in?
They wouldn't tell us
the reason or anything.
Why don't we just let them in?
Setting aside the detective's attitude,
it means the police
will take responsibility.
As Immigration, don't we
just have to comply?
You're right! Shall we do that then?
Um…
If you talk about responsibility,
there's also the responsibility
of letting them in.
Well, when you put it that way…
Um…
At present, the grounds for refusing entry
to those two are weak.
-I suppose so.
-That doesn't mean you can just…
Excuse me!
Um…
Wait, wait, Mori.
What are you doing?
Making my own kind of hand signal.
-Excuse me?
-I'm glad you noticed.
That was a signal just now?
Yes. Um…
-Regarding these dolls…
-Dolls?
What are you talking about?
Ah, the ones Lylea said
were a wedding gift.
Yes.
The shape of these arms
forms a semaphore signal.
Semaphore signal?
It's like flag signaling.
It conveys letters of the alphabet
through arm angles.
This shape is "E". And
this one is "M".
E, M?
Emergency?
Yes. It means an emergency situation.
Wait a minute.
These dolls are saying that?
Or rather, did someone move
these dolls' arms to convey that?
I don't know.
However, I thought this might
also be some kind of sign.
Is that woman asking for help?
Well, it might just be a coincidence
that they're in this shape.
Mori, how do you even know
about these signals?
May I investigate this in more detail?
What, Mori?
I want to investigate a bit more too.
To me, it looked like Lylea was terrified.
What about you, Hayami?
Aren't you a pro at seeing through people?
What if she really
is asking for help?
Even if we investigate…
wouldn't it just be a waste of time?
It doesn't matter if it's a waste, right?
That's our job, isn't it?
Are you done yet? Huh?
Are you done yet? Yes, no?
May we inspect your luggage one more time?
Fine. Whatever. Fine. Okay, okay.
-Thank you.
ANALYZING
This is called TDS--
It's a machine that wipes
the luggage surface
to check for traces of drugs
or explosives.
Right?
Did you come to help out?
No, this is a customs officer's work.
Did anything come up?
NOTHING FOUND
No traces of illegal substances
were detected.
A swing and a miss, then.
If you're just here to mock us,
could you leave?
Um…
Regarding these keys…
Each one of them has their own keys?
What could these keys be for?
This one is for a car, maybe.
The other is a motorcycle and… a padlock?
Then, what about this one?
A front door key? For the couple's home.
I think so too.
But it's strange.
That couple seems to be living
in the same home.
In that case, shouldn't each spouse
have one front door key?
Indeed…
It means only one of them
has the key to the house.
-Is that normal?
-No, it's strange.
Are those two really a married couple?
Hey, Hayami,
since when do you do Customs work?
Excuse me.
I'm also curious about this key.
What key could it be?
A key to a warehouse
somewhere or something?
You notice a lot of things, don't you,
Mori? Your knowledge is broad too.
What were you doing up until now?
Are you listening?
Oh, are you in the middle of something?
We looked into that couple.
Tamai reached out to all her connections
across the airport.
We were able to hear from staff
knowledgeable about international crime.
You have acquaintances like that?
I live purely on human connections.
Endo also looked into local news articles.
For Quarantine, information
is life, after all. Low-key.
And from that,
we found out that right now,
a human trafficking group from Zafaria
is active across all of Asia.
That organization
doesn't just target the individual,
but their entire family as well, it seems.
-The entire family?
-Then,
those two…
Samir
is a broker for the organization,
and Lylea's family was taken hostage,
and she was brought to Japan
against her will,
or so I presume.
Seriously?
But that makes everything add up.
They're a fake couple,
which is why there was only one house key.
Plus, Lylea has been
to Japan multiple times,
so she's highly valuable to Samir.
For getting through
immigration inspection too.
-That's true.
-Hey.
-What do you think?
-What are you going to do?
You're not being very clear.
In the end, Hayami, you just don't
want to take responsibility, right?
Now, now, it's still speculation.
For now, let's report to Fukasawa.
You haven't let them into the country yet?
Well, yes, the police
had also caught onto the possibility
that Samir was connected
to a human trafficking ring.
You wanted to let him enter
rather than arrest him here,
to get the tail of the organization.
Was that the goal?
So that's what's going on…
-But we can't at least protect Lylea?
-Doing something like that
would be as good as notifying
the target that the police suspect them.
Well, that's true…
Hey, what even is this place?
Are you sharing Immigration Intelligence
with Customs and Quarantine here?
-Well, that's…
-Yes.
A special unit that transcends
the boundaries
between ministries and agencies.
This is Gate 24.
Right?
-Something like that's impossible.
-Right?
At any rate, hurry up the procedures.
If the target catches wind
of the police presence, it's all over.
Can you take responsibility
if that happens?
-Understood.
-Alright.
Hey, Hayami…
-It's a police request.
-Even so,
Are you just going
to leave Lylea with him?
Even though she sent a help signal?
Is Immigration fine with that?
It's not my call.
Don't say it so lightly.
Customs can't even take responsibility,
so you should stay out of this.
Well, now, thank you, everyone,
for your hard work.
Fukusawa…
-I am Chief Hearing Officer Fukasawa.
-Oh, hello.
I have heard the circumstances.
The final decision regarding entry
will be made by me.
Then give the go-ahead now.
Don't be in such a rush.
Actually, officials
from the Ministry of Justice
and National Police Agency
are currently conferring on this matter.
Let's wait for their conclusion,
or would acting on your own in the field
turn into a responsibility issue itself?
What are you doing?
Investigating.
That's enough.
There's nothing more
the front line can do.
It's just as the police said.
A unit like this was impossible.
Immigration and Customs
are completely different.
Customs looks at goods. If there's
something illegal, they stop it.
If not, they let it pass.
It's black and white.
But Immigration deals with people.
More often than not,
it can't be divided into black or white.
So while it remains gray,
a line has to be drawn somewhere.
You should just call it quits too now.
Because this matter
is already covered in gray.
Um…
What color is that gray?
-Excuse me?
-Even if you say it's gray,
there are many kinds.
Gray close to white, gray close to black.
Gray mixed with blue or red.
There are countless types.
What color gray is this matter?
I want to know that.
Because I dislike leaving things
I don't understand unknown.
This zipper…
Look, this zipper is made
of flexible resin and is easy to close.
What about it?
What are you doing there?
Counselor Sugihara…
A conclusion has been reached.
They say to grant entry to the two.
So we're just going
to leave Lylea with him…
I'm worried, but I suppose
it can't be helped.
Well then, Hayami,
could I ask you to handle
their entry procedures?
Are you unhappy with something?
No, it's a decision from above.
It's just
this one thing.
I've been bothered
by this photo the whole time.
Everyone in the family is smiling,
but somehow, they look tense.
Tense?
For instance…
-Okay, say cheese!
-What if when this photo was taken,
-Okay!
-Lylea
and her entire family
had already been abducted
and a gun was being pointed
at them from behind the camera?
Even if we let those two pass like this,
I wonder if Lylea's family
will really be okay?
That said, it's just speculation.
Besides, it's too late now.
No,
it's worth investigating.
Shall I negotiate with the top
to buy us just a little more time?
In the meantime,
whether it's a clue about the organization
or Lylea's family, anything goes.
Find grounds enough to stop those two.
-No, but, like I said, this was just--
-Let's do it.
If it comes down to responsibility,
I will take it.
Incredible…
-So cool…
-All right, let's go, go, go.
Apologies for keeping you waiting.
-I am Chief Hearing Officer Fukasawa.
-What now?
How long do you plan
on keeping us for? Huh?
I am very sorry.
Last step. Please allow us to speak
with each of you individually.
One by one, huh? One by one?
Starting with yourself.
I refuse. No. No!
If you comply,
we won't detain you any longer.
Okay, but this is it.
After, you'll let us go.
This way, please.
What's going on? What?
He won't be back for a while.
Could you tell me in detail
about the situation
you are currently in?
I see. So they split the two up.
-I hope it goes well.
-It comes down to Hayami, then…
We got some time. But only 30 minutes.
That's short…
Lylea.
We got the message in your luggage.
We also have a lead on that man
and that your family
is currently in a dangerous situation.
All we need now is to hear it from you.
Please, speak to us.
Look, there's no time.
Let's search for evidence over here too.
-Yes, ma'am.
You tell us to look for evidence, but…
Don't the police have any information?
Like the identity of the organization.
We don't know their exact base,
but we've narrowed it down to some extent.
Whereabouts?
-We can't tell you that.
-That's right.
Um…
Is that base in Aichi Prefecture?
That's right. What?!
This photo is strange.
-This tree looks like a Hananoki.
-Hananoki?
It's a tree unique to Japan.
It's distributed mainly in limited areas
of the Chubu region
and is also the prefectural tree
of Aichi Prefecture.
It shouldn't be seen in Zafaria.
What? Then, this photo was…
Taken in Japan?
Excuse me a second here.
Then what about this utility pole?
Doesn't it provide some clue?
I don't see anything.
I don't know if it will, but…
Utility poles have plates with
identification numbers written on them,
which serve as the address
of the utility pole.
That's a huge clue.
Lylea, please, tell us the truth.
We will protect you and your family
with all our strength.
Please, trust us.
Are you really going to protect me?
Of course.
That man…
is not my husband.
The truth is…
Okay. Let us through.
Wait.
We apologize,
but entry cannot be permitted.
You are suspected of being involved
with a human trafficking organization.
What the hell are you talking about? No.
Fukusawa, what's going on?
We located the place
where your family was being confined.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
-Entire family found.
-Clear!
Don't move!
-What now?
-Hey!
What was that?
It wasn't me. It was not me.
-Bring him up.
-Stand up.
Hideout suppressed. Family secured.
Also…
from the criminal group at the hideout,
we obtained information on the broker,
who was the mastermind.
Lylea Sadikova. Or rather,
real name, Nadia Karimova.
-Don't move!
-Stop!
-Don't touch me!
Stop resisting!
We're borrowing a room.
Let me go!
My family? Are they safe?
Yes.
It's okay now.
H-how?
Those dolls were giving
a signal asking for help.
But there was one more signal.
The zipper on this suitcase
has a structure that doesn't catch easily.
And yet, Samir…
Mori said it caught her attention,
so we investigated.
Take a look.
The shape of his hand at this moment.
A hand signal…
-The same signal as those dolls.
-Yes.
An internationally known signal.
The meaning of this hand signal is
-"help".
-"Help."
The one asking for help was Samir.
We also established contact with Zafaria.
This is your family.
They were abducted by the organization
and brought to Japan, right?
If anything happened to Lylea, the broker,
your family would be in danger.
That's why you couldn't
tell anyone, right?
But it's okay now.
-Why didn't you tell us?
-I'm very sorry!
You were trying
to persuade Lylea at the time.
Besides, when we tried to tell you,
-Mori…
-Um…
You got angry and said that
Customs should just stay out of it.
So if you knew that I,
from Customs, had spoken up,
I was sure you'd be angry again.
So we decided not to tell you.
Are you angry after all?
He's not angry. Right, Hayami?
Samir.
First, I apologize.
We could not stop your family from being
brought into this country at the border.
So that the same thing
never happens again,
we will fulfill our duties
with even greater resolve.
Your family is waiting.
Please go meet them.
Welcome to Japan.
Thank you.
It really is far.
Counselor.
Good work today.
Who on earth is that Machi Mori girl?
Are you that frustrated
about being outsmarted?
Well, she said it was
her first time in the field.
I wondered why such a rookie
was put on this team.
Because I put her in.
Just kidding.
An interesting girl, isn't she?
I'm looking forward to what's to come.
Machi! Hey!
Chika!
Take a seat, please.
That was quite a tough day, huh?
Right?
Here you go.
What a cute girl.
Is she a friend of yours, Chika?
Yup. Eat up, Machi.
The inari sushi here is the best in Japan.
She's exaggerating.
But the love put into it
is number one in the world.
Thank you for the meal.
Man, I'm really glad
to be working at the same airport as you.
Hey, why are you in Customs
in the first place?
You didn't say a word about that.
Because I like objects.
I knew that much.
And…
Well, whatever.
Here, eat up, eat up.
-Oh my!
-Right?
Hey, Ayako, she says it's great!
MIDORI SUGIHARA
COUNSELOR OF BORDER CONTROL REFORM
T-there's a bomb threat.
These 23 individuals
are subject to strict inspection.
Why was tonight's flight to Rome targeted?
-It's almost time.
-Wait, Machi!
What are you doing?
Get down!
Subtitle translation by: Maslin Friedman